Who's there? Who am
I? What's happening?
What is this place?
It's your fault.
There's nothing they can say!
Did I do this?
I can't think straight.
Do it.
Abnormal activity detected.
System failure.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
System failure.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
Hello?
Security system breach.
Abnormal activity detected.
System Failure.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
Hey.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
Station standby power activated.
Hello?!
Hello?
Where am I?
Brion.
Vital oxygen levels compromised.
Riya.
Pass.
Oh, come on.
- Someone's gotta say something.
- Uh.
How about...
we will prosper here. Huh?
What?
- Yeah, yeah.
- What?
- "We will prosper here."
- Right?
What the hell does
that even mean?
- What are you, the queen?
- I think it's nice.
- Nah?
- Nice? Nice is fucking boring.
All right, folks, here we go.
In honour of our dear
friend in the Orbital,
five delicious bowls of
Brion's boiled beans.
To Brion.
- Hmm.
- To Brion.
- Yeah.
- So, Clarke, you, uh...
you think you got
something better?
- Hmm.
- No.
Ask Riya.
Chances are she's gonna
be the first one out.
I am?
Don't look at me.
- Nah, come on, guys.
- How about you, Cap?
Yeah, let's go, Cap. Come on.
I say we should
focus on our mission.
- Oh!
- This guy.
Captain Syed Audie,
first man to set foot
- on planet K.O.I.-442...
- Mm-hmm.
...and his famous
first words were...
- Delicious.
- Guys.
- Shit.
- Fucking savory.
Let's say it's you, then.
What is it?
You're one small step.
Come on.
You really think we're
gonna head out soon?
Yeah, probably.
I mean, uh, this planet, like...
The fact that the atmosphere
is almost breathable already,
like, I... I would be shocked
if any of the others
found something
even close to this viable.
You know what you're doing?
- You're doing your little thing.
- No. No.
- She's good.
- Oh!
- I know.
- I see it. I see it.
- Riya. Riya. Riya.
- Guys, okay.
- Riya. Ri...
- Okay, guys, guys. Okay.
- Oh God. I hate you.
- Come on, you love us.
Okay.
Come on.
- Um.
- Yep?
I'm thinking...
I'm thinking, um...
How about...
let's not fuck it up this time.
Yeah.
- Wow - What?
Kind of a downer?
Come on, guys, I don't
even want to do this.
Cheers.
Who am I?
"Oxygen saturation."
"Cabin pressure"
Movement detected at Zone One.
Exterior airlock.
- Who are you?
- Riya!
What the fuck?
It's me.
Brion.
Brion Cargyle.
Here. Look.
I'm Seven-F.
We're on the same crew. Okay?
I'm orbital monitoring.
- Brion?
- That's right.
Brion.
Brion's boiled beans.
Boiled beans.
Yeah. That's me.
You sent me a distress call.
An SOS.
Said that Clarke had some
sort of psychotic break.
Turned on the crew.
Is she the one that
did this to you?
Davis too?
I'm sorry.
When... when I woke up...
everything had already happened.
What had already happened?
What do you remember?
Um...
Just...
moments.
Images.
A woman.
- Attacking us. I...
- Clarke.
Any idea where she might be?
No. When I woke up,
there was no one left.
That's all you remember?
I'm sorry. I...
It's just everything
that is going on.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know who I am.
Wait here.
- Welcome to Medbot.
- Yes.
You said Seven-F.
What does it mean?
Mission and vessel.
Wait.
Do you not remember Earth?
At all?
No.
Medbot is now scanning,
please remain calm.
Missions one through six failed.
Seven's our final hope.
Half a dozen vessels
spread across the galaxy.
Targeting viable
Earth-sized planets.
- Mission Seven. Vessel F.
- Mm-hmm.
That's us.
And we have the great honor of
calling K.O.I.-442 our home.
Or Ash.
As Kev used to call it.
Hey, hey, hey. It's
okay. It's okay.
I know, it's weird. Just...
just try to stay calm.
You okay?
Yeah.
How come you were
able to stay in orbit.
That's how it works. For
the first year, at least.
One of us has to stay up there.
To establish comms
with home base.
Or, well, if
anything goes wrong.
I think I saw you.
A light across the sky.
- Is that the Orbital?
- That's the one.
Every couple days we line-up.
Next phase beginning,
please remain calm.
Thank you
for using Medbot.
Hey, have you been
experiencing any fever spikes?
Uh, yeah. Actually, just
right before you got here.
I found something in
the emergency kit.
I just put it on. It was a patch.
All right. All done.
Anything stand out?
Nothing major.
There's some swelling
in the brain.
Most likely caused by
blunt force trauma.
But fever, memory loss.
It says here they're all
side effects of the swelling.
But I'll remember everything
eventually, right?
You should still have
your technical memory
and all the skills
that you've learned.
No.
I... I mean...
about me.
Who I am.
What happened here.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
A while back on
the way out here.
You and I. We were talking
about why we joined the program?
There's something about
the way you spoke.
Like, it wasn't about
making a sacrifice.
It was about needing answers.
Like what was out there.
Wasn't enough for you.
See, you don't
remember who you are.
But somehow you're
still exactly the same.
Get some rest.
What are you looking at?
I can't imagine her
still being out there.
If she is, she's got to be
running low on oxygen by now.
She may have tried
to find shelter.
Sandstorms out
here are no jokes.
Maybe we can find her.
I saw a drone somewhere.
Which you're planning
to pilot how?
Yeah.
Shit.
What if she needs our help?
Maybe she got infected
by something out there.
Lost her mind. Killed everyone.
We need to forget about Clarke.
Listen, the station
is on standby.
Running basic life
support systems only.
We're running out of oxygen.
So what's the plan after this?
We need to get off this
planet as soon as possible.
That is our priority.
Everything else, including...
trying to figure out what
the fuck happened here,
has to come second.
Talking big picture.
Big picture.
First, we got to get
back up to the Orbital.
Which ain't easy.
Our rotation and satellite's
orbit have to line-up exactly.
Next line-up is in 12 hours.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
I just need a second.
Riya.
Riya?
You cool?
Yeah, I'm cool.
You don't seem cool.
Hey, I'm fine. I'm just...
I'm tired. That's all. I
haven't slept that well.
It's your patch. It's out of
juice. If you want, I can go...
I just need you to
give me fucking space.
I'm sorry.
I'm just tired. That's all.
What's happening?
What is happening?
I'm sorry about earlier.
Hey, man. It's cool. I get it.
We're all dealing with some
pretty meteoric shit right now.
You know...
I've started to remember things.
Yeah?
Like what?
This is about Kev?
Yeah.
How do I know if it's true?
If this is about the
two of you being a...
a thing, then yeah.
It's true.
This station's about to
handle much worse than this.
Hull breach. Oxygen
levels critical.
Where is it?
There's gotta be a hole in
the structure somewhere.
Brion, in here.
- Why is this open?
- Oh, shit.
Vital oxygen levels compromised.
How much time do we have?
Every minute we don't fix this,
we lose ten hours
of breathable air.
Okay, I'm going in.
Pressure loss imminent.
It's tight in here.
So small.
Oxygen levels in all
sectors at critical level.
Someone's been in here?
Yeah, probably tried
some sort of manual fix
for the system failure.
Just hit 75.
I can hear something.
It's gotta be just ahead of you.
I hear some noise
coming through the back.
Hey, what's going on?
Brion, I need to get off
comms. It's too tight.
Work fast, Ri.
You're practically
breathing poison in there.
Riya?
There you are.
Alright.
So, we are going off the theory,
and correct me if I'm wrong,
that Clarke came into contact
- with some sort of...
- A pathogen, yes.
Somewhere out there.
And it triggered some
sort of psychotic break.
Right?
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
Alright, so maybe
this infection...
is changing her.
- Like rabies, or...
- Yeah. I mean, I don't know. Yes.
Yeah, maybe, but...
It's just something
is not adding up.
Yeah, well, it's
not gonna add up.
I mean, not for a while.
You know, we're still missing
most of the picture here.
Well, we fill it in.
That's what we're gonna do
the next few days, right?
What?
What? Say it.
We just lost 30% of our oxygen.
We don't have time
to fill anything in.
Okay, we have to take the
next line-up in five hours.
We have no answers. We have
more questions. We can't...
Riya! You are not
listening to me, okay?
It is tonight, or we die.
All right? We suffocate.
And all of this, all of
this was for nothing.
We're just gonna
leave her behind.
We're gonna leave Clarke behind?
We don't have a choice, Ri.
Not with the time frame that
we are working with. Okay?
We still have to make
it back to my lander,
and that's 25 minutes easy.
Okay? And we still don't
even know what the fuck
is going on with Clarke.
Okay? She is not worth the risk.
Okay.
Hey, hey.
Riya, we will get to the
bottom of this. I promise.
You good?
Yes. I'm good.
Sometimes I feel like
I could close my eyes
and be back on Earth.
But being here is the
start of something.
Not a reminder of
what we've done.
We're finally here.
Riya.
It hurts.
Now, I know there's
not a lot out there,
but I'm not really
missing Earth much.
This place is amazing.
You'd leave in a
heartbeat for a pizza.
Okay.
I don't think I'll ever
get used to these views.
Mm, mm.
I like the view of you
in that space suit.
You really said that.
Shut up.
My room is right next
to both of theirs.
Oh, I know!
Stop, guys.
- Just imagine the sounds.
- Guys, focus, come on.
- I can hear it too.
They can't help themselves.
My man is terrible.
Guys, I think we're
getting closer.
It's got to be here.
Are you sure? Because
if you're not...
You're going to
cook dinner tonight.
That's a fucking no.
Yeah, no. Yeah, please no.
- Please no.
- Oh, you're what?
What are you guys talking about?
All we have is beans and rice.
I need no more of that shit.
Hey, guys, I think we're here.
This is the exact
spot that Brion
pinpointed the emissions to.
Really?
It's just past these rocks.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Can you believe it?
- Holy shit. Look at this.
- This is insane.
Oh my God.
Kevin. Home.
- Dude, I knew it.
- They were right.
It's fucking manufactured.
This is amazing.
The whole atmosphere is
manufactured. They made it.
How many of these are there?
Across the whole planet?
Dozens, maybe
hundreds, maybe more.
At least to the extent that
Brion could observe it.
Emission signatures, they
get a little diffused
by the time they reach
orbit. I mean, this is it.
- We did it, guys. We did it.
- Holy shit!
Let's go.
- How deep is it?
- Whoa!
Hang on, let me find out.
Just... just be
careful, all right?
Oh, you guys, come
on. I can handle it.
One. Two.
Three. Four. Five.
Whoa.
Hang on, guys.
I think I see...
Davis!
No!
Oh my God!
Careful! Careful!
Guys! Guys!
What's happening?
We gotta get out of here.
What are we doing
here. Let's go!
What's this?
You knew.
What are you talking about?
You can explain, right?
Listen to me.
I didn't know.
Not for sure.
I knew that you went on a
mission, but you went dark.
The entire station
went dark, okay?
I didn't know that this
was how... how Dav...
You knew why we were out there.
You knew.
Kevin talks about it
in the fucking video.
This entire time you saw me
go around in fucking circles
over and over trying to decipher
what the fuck had happened
to Kevin, to Clarke,
to Audie, to Davis.
I was going fucking crazy
when the entire time you knew
this planet was
being terraformed.
There was a window.
Okay, I had a
mission and a window,
and the only way to
fulfill the mission
was to keep things
under control during...
To keep me under control! Me!
Because I know you,
okay? I know how you are.
You may have lost your memory,
but you haven't changed at all.
Okay, why can't you just
let it go? For once.
For once, until we are up
there. Until we are safe.
Because I killed them.
What?
What'd you...
I killed Kev.
I killed Audie, and I...
I just don't know...
I don't know why I did it.
I don't.
I just...
If we leave this station,
I'm never gonna know.
I... I... I need to know.
Brion, I need to know. I can't leave.
-Hey, hey, hey.
What are you saying to me?
I don't...
I don't know why I did it.
These patches...
When they're fading, I've...
I start having more memories.
I can remember everything,
and it comes back faster.
Maybe... maybe we can...
we can wait for two more hours.
They've been coming
quicker and quicker.
Not a chance. Not a chance.
- Why not?!
- Because I don't trust you!
Okay?!
All right, listen to me.
I...
I trust you. I just don't
know the person that did this.
Okay? And I don't know
who you would become
if you stopped
using these things.
We were gonna go up there.
What if I...
- if I don't remember?
- Then you don't remember.
And you live with it.
Riya.
Listen to me.
You and I...
we have a purpose.
Okay?
We sacrificed our lives on Earth
to come out here for a reason.
This.
This is about our species.
The big picture.
Okay? What we have
uncovered here,
proof of alien intelligence
somewhere out there.
There is technology
to mold planets.
This could change the fate
of our entire existence.
Our priority has to be about
the preservation of our mission.
Do you understand this?
Riya.
Tell me that you get this.
I just want to make
sure that we're...
we're good.
Yeah, we're good. I'm
just getting ready.
How long till line-up?
Lander takes off in two
hours and 39 minutes.
A couple clicks east of here.
You all patched up?
Yes.
Put one 30 minutes ago.
Is that enough?
You said they're
getting less effective.
Come on.
There we go.
That's good as new.
I'll come get you
when it's time to...
head out.
Brion I...
Audie, no!
No!
Audie, no.
Stop!
No!
Brion?
It wasn't just Clarke.
They're all infected.
Brion?
Welcome to Medbot.
Medbot is now scanning,
please remain calm.
Medbot scan completed.
What?
No.
No, no, there has to
be something else.
There has to be something else.
Fuck!
Orbital line-up
window is now open.
Come on.
No. No. No.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Oh fuck.
Fuck. Fuck!
Welcome to Medbot.
Medbot scan completed.
Fifty-one hours ago.
What is going on?
What is happening?
It's your fault.
Abnormal activity detected.
Unusual life form detected.
Hello?
What are you?
You used me.
You used me to kill her.
You...
you are...
the infection.
A part of you.
You...
will understand.
Let me show you.
What the hell is that thing?
How long's it been here?
Maybe it came back with you.
Orbital to ground station.
Ground station, do you copy?
The data transfer's
interrupted. Please respond.
Ground station, do you copy?
This is the Orbital.
Ground station, please respond.
- Riya, step back.
- It's everywhere.
Take a sample.
Bring it to the lab.
Movement detected at Zone One.
Exterior airlock.
What the fuck happened to Davis?
It seems like it attached
itself to our mainframe.
Yeah, it spread from there.
I dug a hole in the
wall to see how far.
And it's... it's mostly isolated
to the airlock and the control room.
-For now.
What if it's been studying
us ever since we landed?
Exactly. Waiting for the
right moment to shut us down.
When's the next line-up?
Huh?
The next line-up. When is it?
- Thirteen hours.
- Got it.
I'll pack up the lab and I'll meet you...
-No, no, wait.
- We're leaving.
- Riya, we're following protocol.
Fuck the protocol.
This is what we've been waiting...
-No!
Protocol exists for a reason.
We need to get out of here
before that thing spreads.
Protect the mission.
-The mission? This is the mission.
Do you guys remember
why we signed up?
All of us.
Everything we sacrificed.
That the best case scenario, we
would grow old light years away
from everything
we've ever known.
It's out there.
Right now.
An actual solution. The
technology to create a new world
where we don't get poisoned
by the air we're breathing.
Self-replicating technology.
What are you doing?
Audie...
Audie, this could be our answer.
Back the fuck up!
Audie!
No. No. No.
Audie?
What the fuck?! Riya!
Whoa! Whoa!
- Riya.
- What the fuck?
Abnormal activity detected.
Riya, what have you done?
Oh shit!
Throw me!
Kevin.
Kevin?
Riya!
Abnormal activity detected.
You okay?
- Riya!
- Clarke.
Come on, we gotta get
the fuck out of here!
Go.
Riya!
Clarke!
Abnormal activity detected.
Help her.
Fuck.
Oh fuck.
Clarke.
You gotta go.
Go to the lander.
I have to stay.
Riya.
It's me.
Kevin.
Did I do this?
It's okay.
It's all my fault.
You can say it. I'm sorry.
Hey.
Remember.
It's okay.
Abnormal activity detected.
Take it, Riya.
You're all alone.
You're gonna die.
You didn't do this.
You killed them all.
I'm scared. Am I crazy?
Unusual parasitic
activity detected.
I don't want
More.
Fuck your existence.
Oxygen levels in all
sectors at critical level.
Vital oxygen levels compromised.
Welcome to Medbot.
Medbot is now scanning,
please remain calm.
Scanning completed.
Next phase beginning,
please remain calm.
What the...
Fuck you!
Come on. Come on.
♪ A host ♪
♪ I claim you ♪
♪ As my own ♪
♪ Even if some ♪
♪ Wanted to ♪
♪ Obey ♪
♪ In your dreams ♪
♪ I, I saw ♪
♪ Sweet dream ♪
♪ In your head ♪
♪ My dreams ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Keep ♪